https://greennature.com/privacy/

Skip to content
Menu Field GuidesAnimalsBirdsButterfliesDragonfliesInsectsSpidersHerpsFrogsLizardsSnakesTurtlesHome and GardenFlowersGarden TipsMushroomsLawn Care0 SharesShareGreen Nature takes privacy rights seriously.The data collected by registered members starts with their name and a valid email address. Member profile information is voluntary added by individual members and can be edited and changed at member discretion. No child under the age of 13 may register as a member of Green Nature.Green Nature also collects additional information such as visitor IP addresses, time visitors and members are on the site, time members login the site, and other information contained in our server log files.Twitter currently defines their privacy policy for sites such as Gratography who voluntarily use a Twitter widget as follows:When you view Twitter content or Twitter products integrated into other websites using Twitter for Websites, Twitter may receive information including the web page you visited, your IP address, browser type, operating system, and cookie information.YouTube enhanced privacy is turned on for the embedded videos. According to the YouTube policy for enhanced privacy:When you turn on privacy-enhanced mode, YouTube won’t store information about visitors on your website unless they play the video.Similar policies also apply to the site advertisers. They send cookies and collect data, independent of this web site. As adevertisers are added to the site, their specific privacy policies will be added to this page.SecurityThe security of your Personal Information is important to us, but remember that no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure. While Green Nature strives to use commercially acceptable means to protect your Personal Information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.Changes To This Privacy PolicyThis Privacy Policy is effective as of August 13, 2018 and will remain in effect except with respect to any changes in its provisions in the future, which will be in effect immediately after being posted on this page.We reserve the right to update or change our Privacy Policy at any time and you should check this Privacy Policy periodically. Your continued use of the Service after we post any modifications to the Privacy Policy on this page will constitute your acknowledgment of the modifications and your consent to abide and be bound by the modified Privacy Policy.If we make any material changes to this Privacy Policy, we will notify you by placing a prominent notice on our website.
Search for:
